[
  {
    "question": "What is Moaning Myrtle's real name?",
    "answer": "Myrtle Warren"
  },
  {
    "question": "What do wizards call people who were born into wizarding families but don't have any powers?",
    "answer": "Squibs"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Gryffindor motto?",
    "answer": "Forti Animo Estote"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Dobby the House Elf call Ron Weasley?",
    "answer": "Wheezy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of animal does Ginny kill while possessed by Boldemort in Chamber of Secrets?",
    "answer": "Roosters"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the first names of the Patil sisters?",
    "answer": "Parvati and Padma"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Harry's favorite dessert?",
    "answer": "Treacle Tart"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Diagon Alley shop sells robes, uniforms and other various school supplies?",
    "answer": "Madam Malkin's Robes for All Occasions"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell is used to banish a boggart?",
    "answer": "The Riddikulus spell"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the type of magical bowl that displays memories in a liquid, vapor form?",
    "answer": "A Pensieve"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do the Weasleys go on vacation with their winnings?",
    "answer": "Egypt"
  },
  {
    "question": "What speciality is Minerva McGonagall a professor of?",
    "answer": "Transfiguration"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which family wins the Daily Prophet Grand Prize Galleon Draw?",
    "answer": "The Weasleys"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Uncle Vernon's sister, Marge Dursley, do for a living?",
    "answer": "She's a bulldog breeder"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the conductor of the Knight Bus?",
    "answer": "Stan Shupnik"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is cast by Professor McGonagall in Deathly Hallows: Part 2 to animate the Hogwarts statues?",
    "answer": "Piertotum Locomotor"
  },
  {
    "question": "When Hermoine is petrified by the basilisk in Chamber of Secrets, what cures her?",
    "answer": "Professor Sprout's Mandrake Restorative Draught"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why couldn't Jacob get a loan for his bakery from the bank?",
    "answer": "He didn't have any collateral"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the wizarding school in America?",
    "answer": "Ilvermorny"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Nagini?",
    "answer": "A Maladictus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the magazine where Tina read about Newt's supposed engagement to Leta Lestrange?",
    "answer": "Spellbound"
  },
  {
    "question": "Newt thinks Tina has eyes just like a what?",
    "answer": "Salamander"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Gnarlack want as payment for information on the escaped beasts?",
    "answer": "Pickett the bowtruckle"
  },
  {
    "question": "After Newt's travel documentation is denied, who takes the job of finding and killing Credence?",
    "answer": "Gunnar Grimmson"
  },
  {
    "question": "How long was Grindelwald kept in custody by MACUSA?",
    "answer": "6 months"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was Crimes of Grindelwald set?",
    "answer": "1927"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the MACUSA headquarters?",
    "answer": "Woolworth Building"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of Newt's beasts bit his assistant Bunty's finger?",
    "answer": "Kelpie"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Ministry of Magic agreed to lift Newt's international travel ban on what condition?",
    "answer": "He joins the Ministry of Magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Hogwarts House was Newt Scamander in?",
    "answer": "Hufflepuff"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does Dumbledore send Newt to Paris?",
    "answer": "To find Credence"
  },
  {
    "question": "After thinking Newt is engaged to Leta Lestrange, who does Tina Goldstein start dating?",
    "answer": "Achilles Tolliver"
  },
  {
    "question": "What beast provides the venom which erases the bad memories of New York muggles?",
    "answer": "The Swooping Evil"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Newt Scamander's Bowtruckle?",
    "answer": "Pickett"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the purpose of Newt Scamander's trip to New York?",
    "answer": "Return Frank the Thunderbird"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell does Newt use on Jacob to lift the effects of the love potion?",
    "answer": "Surgito"
  },
  {
    "question": "What causes an Obscurus to grow, according to Dumbledore?",
    "answer": "Absence of love"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the President of the Magical Congress of the United States of America?",
    "answer": "President Seraphina Picquery"
  },
  {
    "question": "What year did Newt arrive in New York",
    "answer": "1926"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Hogwarts House was Leta Lestrage in?",
    "answer": "Slytherin"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the serpentine-like beast that can grow and shrink to fit the available space?",
    "answer": "Occamy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do Newt and Jacob first meet?",
    "answer": "A bank"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Newt Scamander's Boggart?",
    "answer": "An office desk"
  },
  {
    "question": "What beast do Newt and Jacob capture in Central Park?",
    "answer": "The Erumpent"
  },
  {
    "question": "What core and wood was Fleur Delacores wand?",
    "answer": "Vela hair and Rosewood"
  },
  {
    "question": "Harry disguised himself as Rob’s cousinf, what was his name?",
    "answer": "Barney Weasley"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much did Harry’s first wand cost",
    "answer": "7 Galleons"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name for the art of reading tea leaves?",
    "answer": "Tessaomacy"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many points collectively do Harry, Ron, and Hermione earn for beating the mountain troll?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "When riding the Knight Bus for the first time what name does Harry give to disguise himself?",
    "answer": "Neville Longbottom"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Gray Lady is the ghost of Ravenclaw, what is her real name?",
    "answer": "Helena Ravenclaw"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does N.E.W.T stand for?",
    "answer": "Nastily Exhausting Wizarding Tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Harry Potter’s godfather?",
    "answer": "Sirius Black"
  }
]